A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Division, Office Files of Elinor Barber FA632
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appendix C: Reports: Education/Language/Development
  - Barber, Elinor G. Conference on sociolinguistics surveys, 1975 May (Report 8222)
  - Echols, John M. Indonesia's sociolinguistic situation (Report 8226)
  - Fox, Melvin J. Ford Foundation grants relating to English as a Second Language and related problems (Report 8227)